What the hell are
you trying to say, Severin?
That you're behind all of this?
Who else would risk everything
to help you and your family?
Stop!
Severin, you're insane.
You, a cast-off bastard abandoned by your own family,
expect me to believe you have
connections
in the Sovereign Sanctum?
Livia, I have to-
Stop.
I already know
what's really going on.
It was Redmond.
He used the
Carter name to speak
for me in
front of Steward Jeyn.
That's how my family and I earned this honor.
Redmond introduced you?
Of course it was him.
Who else could it be?
You can be a complete failure, Severin,
but at least be honest.
If the Sovereign Sanctum ever
heard you
say something like that,
they'd erase you.
Just end this engagement already.
You're not worthy of me.
You're so desperate to end this.
Is this about saving your family...
or are you just
eager to marry Redmond?
Don't be ridiculous!
This is all your own failure.
For whatever we had,
just sign the damn papers.
Or you will regret it.
I'll regret it?